(Penny:)Yeah. I'm tapping out.
Leonard?
(Leonard:)I'm gonna guess that your main
concern is the time commitment
(Leonard:)of watching an entire season
of a new show.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, not just a season.
(Sheldon:)If I'm in,
I'm in for the whole run,
(Sheldon:)even if the quality declines.
(Leonard:)I get it.
Smallville almost wrecked you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. Exactly.
(Sheldon:)You know, I waited ten years
(Sheldon:)to see a guy
everyone knows can fly, fly.
(Penny:)Wait, what is wrong
with you two?
(Penny:)He was talking about television
during their date night.
(Sheldon:)Oh, not just date night--
our fifth anniversary.
(Penny:)Okay, see, that's even dumber
than you wondering
(Penny:)if being bitten by a goat would
give you the powers of a goat.
(Sheldon:)If that happens,
don't make me wait ten years
(Sheldon:)to watch you eat a tin can.
(Raj:)You guys ever notice that Emily
has a bit of a twisted side?
(Bernadette:)You mean
'cause she has weird tattoos?
(Raj:)No, because she wants to have
sex with me in a graveyard.
(Howard:)One more time?